tellyreviews.com 2019-10-11

# Privacy Policy - TellyReviews

**TellyReviews.com** is referred below in one of the following ways: “Site” or “we”, “our” or “us”. We put dedicated efforts to protect your privacy and wants you to have seamless, secure and comfortable experience whilst you visit our site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by TellyReviews.com. 

**1\. Collection of data**

The following three types of data are collected by us. Non-personally identifiable information: IP address, device type of access, operating systems, referral website. We make sure to anonymize collected IP address so users’ privacy is strictly enforced. Second, we may collect personally identifiable information (such as name, e-mail address, gender) only when user membership registration is allowed and possible on our site (currently this service isn’t available on our site). As a registered user, you would be able to access and use our services (submitting reviews and opinion articles, responding to your inquiries on privacy) which we envision to realise in then near future.

**2\. Use of data**

The data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement. 

**3\. Cookies**

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. Advertisements may be displayed on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site’s cookies. 

**4\. Advertising**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information which we describe earlier such as IP address, device and browser type, geolocation, type of advertisement clicked or viewed during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide context driven or personalized advertisements about products and services that are likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon through gifs to collect this information. 

**5\. Complying with EU GDPR regulation**

For visitors coming to our website from EU or EU nationals, we comply with GDPR by regularly updating our website CMS with the latest version of WordPress which is updated to be GPDR-compliant always, also making sure our theme and plugins are GDPR-compliant. We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. All these Ad networks have updated their privacy policies to comply with GDPR regulation and EU user consent policies, please check their respective privacy policies. 

**6\. Changes to this privacy policy**

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy by means of an announcement via post on the site.

**7\. NO GUARANTEES**

While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, TellyReviews.com and its site administrator are not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data.

**8\. Contact information**

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact the TellyReviews.com site’s administrator: tellyreviews1 [at] gmail [dot] com.
